behringer.com 2015-09-05

# BEHRINGER: Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our Site.  Furthermore, we take the confidentiality of your personal information seriously. This Privacy Policy sets forth our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**What is personal information?**

Personal information is any information that is used to identify a particular person, such as a name, address, telephone number, email address and so on. We will only use such information when we are legally allowed to or when you give us your express consent.

**Your Consent to This Privacy Policy**

By accessing, browsing or using the Site or providing us with your personal information, including but not limited to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address, you signify that you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy as posted in the Site. If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, please do not access, browse or use the Site or provide us with your personal information.

We may alter or remove this Privacy Policy at any time. Whenever we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes here. Therefore, please visit this page frequently to stay informed. When you access, browse or use the Site after the revision of this Privacy Policy, you signify that you agree to the revised Privacy Policy.

**Collection of Personal Information**

While you are accessing, browsing or using the Site, you may be asked for your personal information to allow you to participate in prize competitions, answer our questionnaires or inquiries by e-mail or through the Site, register as a MUSIC Group user, monitor MUSIC Group products, receive e-mail news services concerning the MUSIC Group products, and so on.

We will not collect your personal information unless and until you provide such information to us voluntarily. When you provide us with your personal information, you authorize us to use such information in accordance with the terms set forth below. You may withdraw this authorization anytime by sending instructions through an email to [service@music-group.com](mailto:service@music-group.com) and we will immediately delete all your personal information. 

**How we use your information**

When we collect your personal information, we shall specify the purpose of such collection.

Any personal information that you provide will be used to meet your request such as forwarding brochures, magazines, etc. and offering certain services. We may also use your personal information to contact you regarding other products and services that may be of interest to you. You can send a request to [service@music-group.com](mailto:service@music-group.com) instructing us to limit our contact with you to a specific purpose.

**Sharing of your information**

We may share your personal information with the following:

  * Affiliates and contractors who help with our business operations and are bound to confidentiality. They shall only use your personal information for the sole purpose of assisting MUSIC Group in providing the services you applied for.
  * Law enforcement, judicial authorities or other governmental officials for legal proceedings, fraud prevention, investigations into illegal activities or as otherwise required by law.
  * other business entities, should we plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity.

**Security**

We use technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access.

**Google AdWords**

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise MUSIC Group across the Internet, in particular on the Google Display Network.

AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of the MUSIC Group website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser.

This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device.

The cookie is used to indicate to other websites that “This person visited a particular page, so show them ads relating to that page.”

Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

If you do not wish to see ads from MUSIC Group you can opt out in several ways:

  1. Opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
  2. Opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
